Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series II. Office Records
  - General
    - Maloney, 1959-1965 (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Gabrielli, Haver, 1959 (Box 153, Folder 23)
    - Kingston general, 1957-1962 (Box 153, Folder 24)
    - Builders (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - Purdy (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - Back vs. Jones, 1957-1960 (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - Kingston (Box 153, Folder 28)
    - Duplicate sets of options for Kingston (Box 153, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Economic and Investment analysis, Rye NY (Box 154, Folder 2-3)
    - Rye and Greenwich analysis and map (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Planned Communities, Inc., 1973-1975 (Box 154, Folder 5-8)
    - Oakville, Ontario, 1960 (Box 155, Folder 1-3)
    - Ocala, Florida, 1962 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Oceanside Golf Club, 1949 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Office equipment, 1944-1955 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Office expenses, 931 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Office, 1939-1945 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - O’Hara, Ken, 1957 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Old Oaks Country Club, 1949 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Omaha Country Club, 1952-1953 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Omaha New Group, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Onondaga Country Club, 1948-1954 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Oenoke Country Club, 1944-1945 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Operadio, 1937 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Orchard Lake Country Club, 1953 (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Orlando Country Club, 1957-1961 (Box 155, Folder 17-20)
    - Oyster Harbors Club, 1953 (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1959-1961 (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Ontario Beach Park (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1931-1945 (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Pal's Cabin, 1952 (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - Palm Beach, 1951-1959 (Box 155, Folder 26-27)
    - Parker, Chas, 1952-1955 (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - Passaic County, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 29)
    - Patchogue, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 30)
    - Pageant Magazine Article (Box 155, Folder 31)
    - Patton Republic Steel, 1958 (Box 155, Folder 32)
    - Pelham Country Club, 1942-1954 (Box 155, Folder 33)
    - Pensacola, 1947-1948 (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - Pequabuck Golf Course, 1953 (Box 155, Folder 35)
    - Perfume, 1946-1947 (Box 155, Folder 36)
    - Perkins, Frank, 1955 (Box 155, Folder 37)
    - Peterson, Arthur and Mather manufacturing, 1943-1944 (Box 155, Folder 38)
    - Peru, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 39)
    - Pettycash, 1958 (Box 155, Folder 40)
    - Phillips Foundation, 1959-1960 (Box 155, Folder 41)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 1949 (Box 155, Folder 42)
    - Picatinny Arsenal Golf and Tennis Club, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 43)
    - Pittsburgh Golf Course, 1957 (Box 155, Folder 44)
    - Platt, J Wood, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 45)
    - Playground, Nassau County, 1949-1952 (Box 155, Folder 46)
    - Pittsburgh Field Club, 1951-1954 (Box 155, Folder 47)
    - Plewman, 1953-1955 (Box 155, Folder 48)
    - Ponte Vedra Corporation, 1961-1962 (Box 155, Folder 49)
    - Pontaic MI, 1954 (Box 155, Folder 50)
    - Portland Country Club, 1949-1957 (Box 155, Folder 51)
    - Portland Waverly Country Club, 1950-1956 (Box 155, Folder 52)
    - Portsmouth Country Club, 1955-1961 (Box 155, Folder 53-58)
    - Poughkeepsie, 1957 (Box 155, Folder 59)
    - Pregel (Box 155, Folder 60)
    - Presido Golf Club, 1956-1960 (Box 155, Folder 61)
    - Princeton, 1953-1955 (Box 155, Folder 62-6364)
    - Preakness Hills Country club, 1944-1945 (Box 155, Folder 63)
    - Awards, Balley Bullion, Cornell Foundation, sketches, Bobby Jones Memorial Scholarships, personal info on RTJ, 1990-1998 (Box 170)
    - Three Bays, Inc., Golden Triangle Golf Course, MD - Duckett, 1972-1875 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Three Bays, Inc., Quail Hollow, Hartville, OH - Bart Stewart, 1972 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Three Bays, Inc. Avery Creek, NC, 1972-1973 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Trentwood Development Corp., 1984 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Turf Irrigation, Inc, 1957-1974 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Valley Crest Ranch, 1960-1964 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Valley Crest Ranch - Financial, 1959-1967 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Wage and Hour - Fair Labor and Standards Act, 1964-1967 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Wells Landscape Co. Overseas, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Weyerhaeuser Co. Combustion Power Company, Inc/, 1973-1976 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Wisconsin River Development Corp., 1968-1970 (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Old Warson country club, 1950-1965 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Office Hinck building, 1970-1987 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Pan American Airways employment agreement, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Parkin, Bob, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Pension data and proposals, 1972 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Pollock Corporation, 1975 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1973 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Ponico, John, 1977-1983 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Projects, general, 1969 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rican Golf Corporation, 1979-1982 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Puerto Rico- Cubero, 1970 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Rando Associates, 1963-1973 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Rulewich, Roger, 1961-1963 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Sangre de Cristo claim, 1980-1983 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Thermal Construction Co., Homer Flint Construction, 1967, 1975 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Three Bays, Incorporated, 1972-1975 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Golden Triangle, Maryland, 1972-1976 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - St. Louis Country Club, 1952-1953 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - St. Louis- Glen Echo Country Club, 1953-1954 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - St. Louis- New Group, 1956-1957 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - St. Louis- Norwood Hills, 1953 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Salem, Oregon, 1959 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Saranac Inn, 1944 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Saratoga Golf and Country Club, 1930 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Sarazen, Gene, 1934-1960 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Scarsdale Country Club, 1944-1962 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Shaub, Robert, 1944-1950 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Schindler, Raymond, 1950-1954 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Schmeisser, John, 1952-1953 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Schoeppl, Carlos, 1960 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Schumacher Property (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Scona, Aluminium company of America, 1956-1958 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Scranton, PA, 1957 (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Sea Island Company, 1937-1952 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Searle, James, 1949-1956 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - SeeKonk MA, 1955 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Sequotah Country Club, 1961 (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - Seminole Beach Golf Course, 1955 (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - Seneca Falls Golf Course, 1954-1955 (Box 181, Folder 22)
    - Service Contracts, 1956-1957 (Box 181, Folder 23)
    - Shady Oaks Country Club, Fort Worth, TX, 1962 (Box 181, Folder 24)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1954 (Box 181, Folder 25)
    - Simpson, Glen, 1948-1949 (Box 181, Folder 26)
    - Simsbury, CT, 1954 (Box 181, Folder 27)
    - Siwanoy country club, 1952-1954 (Box 181, Folder 28)
    - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 1951 (Box 181, Folder 29)
    - Slotter, Groome, 1931-1933 (Box 181, Folder 30)
    - Smith, Phelps, 1937-1938 (Box 181, Folder 31)
    - Sam Snead, 1950-1957 (Box 181, Folder 32)
    - S-T-U Miscellaneous, 1937-1938 (Box 181, Folder 33)
    - Shaw, Robert, 1948-1949 (Box 181, Folder 34)
    - St. Charles Country Club, 1937-1939 (Box 181, Folder 35)
    - Short Course report, 1960s (Box 181, Folder 36)
    - San Antonio, 1946-1947 (Box 181, Folder 37)
    - Sales talk, 1960s (Box 181, Folder 38)
    - Sackett, Paul, 1954-1955 (Box 181, Folder 39)
    - Sawtelle Brothers, 1954 (Box 181, Folder 40)
    - St. Andrews Golf Club (Box 181, Folder 41)
    - St. George's Golf Course, Ontario, 1960-1961 (Box 181, Folder 42)
    - Shaughnessy, Frank, 1943 (Box 181, Folder 43)
    - Sears Roebuck, 1947 (Box 181, Folder 44)
    - Historical, 1987-1996 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Computer Survey, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Biography, News, etc (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Peter Charles, 1988 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Sun Microsystems - Maintenance, 1993 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Lahaina Investment Corp, 1961-1975 (Box 192, Folder 1-3)
    - Lahaina Investment Corp. Proxy control, 1963-1964 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Golf Challenge, 1957-61 (Box 192, Folder 5-9)
    - Golf Challenge players, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Runnymede to JM, 1969-1974 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Johns-Manville realty, 1971 (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Manville, 1973-1982 (Box 192)
    - Continental American Life Insurance Company (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - "C" reports (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - American Golfers Club financial statements, 1990-1996 (Box 210, Folder 3-4)
    - RTJ medical (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Robert Trent Jones Last Will and Testament, 1995 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Checks, 1999 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - American Golfers reports (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - RTJ One hour golf concept (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - US Open Baltustral, 1992-1993 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - RTJ Personal financial (Box 210, Folder 11-12)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 1, 1969 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 1, 1968 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 1, 1961 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 2, 1960s (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 2, 1960s (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 2, 1968 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 3, 1968 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 4, 1969 (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Runnymeade Corporation 5, 1969 (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Binar and Watermatics with Kearny - National, 1967-1969 (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Coral Ridge Golf Course and American Golfers Club, Inc. - Wage and Hour Problems, 1969 (Box 243, Folder 11)
    - Commission Proposals, 1970 (Box 243, Folder 12)
    - Corporate Golf, Inc. - Bill Abbott, 1970 (Box 243, Folder 13)
    - Morris County Real Estate - Ted Flemming 1, 1963-1968 (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - Real Estate - Ted Flemming 2, 1964-1968 (Box 243, Folder 15)
    - Ione and Robert Trent Jones vs. Trans World Airlines, 1968-1969 (Box 243, Folder 16)
    - Davie, FL (4), 1974 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Davie, FL (5), 1976-1978 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Davie, FL (6), 1978-1979 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Davie, FL (7), 1979-1982 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Davie, FL - Partition Action, 1969-1976 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Davie, FL - Ft. Lauderdale Land, taxes [RESTRICTED], 1961-1974 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Davie, FL - Taxes (2) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Davie, FL - Maps and Plans (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Seal - Development Corporation of America (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Club Services Inc., 1966-1976 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Club Services Inc. - Contracts, 1967-1970 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Club Services Inc. - Payroll and Depository, 1971 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Club Services Inc. - Dissolution of Company, 1976 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Club Books, assorted, c.1962-1969 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Membership Rosters, c.1968 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Membership Applications (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Membership Cards, 1970 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and Resumes, 1969-1970 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Score Cards (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Racquet and Tennis Club book, 1967 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Cotton Bay and Raquet Club - Membership Lists (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Rock Spring Club, Essex Fells, NJ, Club books, 1967-1969 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Rossmoor - Brochure, c.1967 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - Roxitucus Golf Club, correspondence, 1967 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - Sea Pines, Hilton Head, SC, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - Sea Pines Plantation, Hilton Head, SC, brochures, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - Silverado Country Club (Box 223, Folder 18)
    - Sleepy Hallow Country Club (Box 223, Folder 19)
    - California Country Clubs - Developments (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - Two Bridges Country Club, 1968-1969 (Box 223, Folder 21)
    - Stuart, FL, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 22)
    - Connecticut Golf Courses brochures (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - New Hampshire Golf Courses brochures, 1969 (Box 223, Folder 24)
    - New Jersey Golf Courses brochures, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 25)
    - New York Golf Courses brochures, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 26)
    - The Spring Green - Ski Marketing correspondence, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 27)
    - The Spring Green - W.H. Keland correspondence, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 28)
    - The Spring Green - Cal Meider correspondence and press, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 29)
    - The Spring Green research and development, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 30)
    - The Spring Green, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 31)
    - Wintergreen, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 32)
    - Wintergreen - Ski Lifts Costs and Specs, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 33)
    - Golf Course Sketches (Box 223, Folder 34)
    - R.S. Knapp - Crag Burn Art for Logo, 1970 (Box 223, Folder 35)
  - Financial Records [RESTRICTED]
    - Sunbank - Payroll Account - Bank Reconciliations, mortgage papers [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Attorney's Title Insurance Fund and The Bank of California [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Retirement Systems of Alabama [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Roy-First Eastern Ipswich Settlement [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Weller-All State Leasing [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Saunders/Bonneau Release [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fenwick and West, Palo Alto, CA [RESTRICTED], 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Lely Flamingo Lakes - Drainage [RESTRICTED], 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Mississippi State University [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Mississippi State University [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Oakmont Country Club [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ipswich - Mortgage Investors of Washington (MIW) Suits - General Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Ipswich - Mortgage Investors of Washington (MIW) Suits - General Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Ipswich - Mortgage Investors of Washington (MIW) Settlement Papers - Originals [RESTRICTED], 1974-1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Ipswich - Mortgage Investors of Washington (MIW) Suits - Formal Papers [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Ipswich - Mortgage Investors of Washington (MIW) Suits - Formal Papers [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Radice - Jones Mortgage - Ipswich Reality Income Trust [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Linksland [RESTRICTED], 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Report of Foreign Bank Accounts [RESTRICTED], 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Robert Trent Jones Companies - Frank Weller [RESTRICTED], 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - American Express [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - The Legends [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Financial Statements [RESTRICTED], 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Check Copies and Bank Reconciliations [RESTRICTED], 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Check Copies and Bank Reconciliations [RESTRICTED], 1999-2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Account Statements (1) [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Account Statements (2) [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Account Statements (1) [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Oper. Bank statements [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Account Statements (2) [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Bank Reconciliations [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Robert Trent Jones Trust and Investment Account [RESTRICTED], 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Cancelled Checks [RESTRICTED], 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Florida Golf Report [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Robert Trent Jones, Florida Inc. - Report [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Sunbank - Bank Reconciliations [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - A/P Reports [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Robert Trent Jones - SunTrust Statements [RESTRICTED], 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Robert Trent Jones - SunTrust Statements [RESTRICTED], 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Personal Account [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Florida Golf Corporation - Bills Paid [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Coral Ridge Golf Course, Ft. Lauderdale, FL - Publicity [RESTRICTED], 2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Domaine de Joyenval - Correspondence and Memos [RESTRICTED], 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Robert Trent Jones Personal (1) [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Robert Trent Jones Personal (2) [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Travel [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Sunbank - Statements [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Owen, Falkins and Nicols - Engagement Letter [RESTRICTED], 1995` (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Medicare Benefits [RESTRICTED], 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Certificate of Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Tax Forms, including 1069, W2, and 1099 [RESTRICTED], 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Taxes and Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Annual Evaluation [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Annual Evaluation [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Florida Golf Corp. - Ledger [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Florida Golf Corp. - Ledger [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Fixed Assets [RESTRICTED], 1969-1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Fixed Assets [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Fixed Assets [RESTRICTED], 1972-1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Purchased Construction Equipment [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Florida Golf Corp. - Financial Statements [RESTRICTED] (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Newell, Michael [RESTRICTED], 1987-1994 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Blackburn, Benton [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Williams, Marc A. [RESTRICTED], 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Alfano, Antoinette M. [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Davis, Alan B. [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Darwell, Marjorie [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Davis, Alan B. [RESTRICTED], 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Gallagher, Marilyn [RESTRICTED], 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Harvey, Arthur J. [RESTRICTED], 1988-1995 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Rasmussem, Steven B. [RESTRICTED], 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Rulewich, Roger [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Rulewich, Roger [RESTRICTED], 1988-1994 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Romano, Donna [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Slessor, Jeremy [RESTRICTED], 1987-1994 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Marshall, Victor [RESTRICTED], 1991-1995 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt, financial records and correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - European Invoices and Statements [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Invoices and Accounts Payable [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Bank Statements [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Adrian Argyle Cooper [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Journal Entries, ledger book [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Insurance Policy [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Expenses - American Express [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Expenses [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Expense Reports - Les Jardins de la Palmeraie, Morroco [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Receipts, Bills and Expense Reports: A-E [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13-17)
    - Receipts, Bills and Expense Reports: F-K [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 18-23)
    - Receipts, Bills and Expense Reports: L-R [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 24-30)
    - Receipts, Bills and Expense Reports: S-Z [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 18, Folder 31-38)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt - Expenses [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Cascade Trust [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Hearts and Spaces Trusts [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Florida Golf Corporation/Golf Developments, Inc. Lawsuit papers [RESTRICTED], 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Management Services, Golf Inc. - Yearly Financial Statements [RESTRICTED], 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Landlord's, Inc. Balance Sheet, Unaudited [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Robert Trent Jones Consulting and Placement, Inc. Articles [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Robert Trent Jones (Florida), Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Robert Trent Jones Foundation - General Corporate [RESTRICTED], 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Cart Accident - Flaskamper [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Estate of Ione Davis Jones - Residence, Rees Lee Jones, Pers. Rep. of [RESTRICTED], 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Estate of Ione Davis Jones - Debt, Rees Lee Jones, Pers. Rep. of [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Estate of Ione Davis Jones - Stock, Rees Lee Jones, Pers. Rep. of [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Life Insurance Policies [RESTRICTED], 1962-1990 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Comfort Care [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Medicare [RESTRICTED], 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - United American Insurance Co. - Medicare Supplemental [RESTRICTED], 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Medicare Supplementary [RESTRICTED], 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Barefield, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - General Personnel, names and addresses [RESTRICTED] (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Bradley, Jeffrey A. [RESTRICTED], 1988-1994 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Wulfmeyer, Bruce A. [RESTRICTED], 1989-1994 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Clemans, D. Allen [RESTRICTED], 1988-1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Darling, Gary [RESTRICTED], 1984-1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Drug Screen Results [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Montclair National Bank - Interest Loans [RESTRICTED], 1962-1970 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Tax Records - Shopping Centers [RESTRICTED], 1961-1971 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - RTJ finance book [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Linksland Golf finances [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - RTJ invoices [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
    - UBS books [RESTRICTED] (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
    - International Planners Anstalt (IPA) [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - International Planners Anstalt (IPA) - Purchases [RESTRICTED], 1987-1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - International Planners Anstalt (IPA) - Payables [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt - Accounts Receivable [RESTRICTED], 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - International Planners Anstalt (IPA) - Cash [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt - Cash [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - International Planners Anstalt (IPA) [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Robert Trent Jones Anstalt - Cash [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Robert Trent Jones S.A. - Cash Books [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 43, Folder 9)